Ricky Edimiente and makes up a
Ricky edimiente y se inventa una orden
restraining order against Dallas review
de alejamiento contra Dallas review
also his ex-girlfriend and he unfollow each other
además su exnovia y él se dejan de
again on social media René
seguir de nuevo en redes sociales René
ZZ the most famous youtuber of
ZZ el youtuber más famoso de los
tattoos gives some very good advice to
tatuajes le da un consejo muy bueno a
Ricky Edith while karcher mocks
Ricky Edith mientras karcher se burla de
him Avi is accused of manipulating karches
él acusan a Avi de manipular a karches
the million receives the best contract of his
el millón recibe el mejor contrato de su
life in Kick Ari Gameplays talks about his
vida en Kick Ari Gameplays habla sobre
Reconciliation with Beijing and
su Reconciliación con Beijing y
denies hoaxes about it also
desmiente bulos sobre ella además
auronplay also speaks out on the
auronplay también se pronuncia sobre el
subject Juan Guarnizo is preparing to be a
tema Juan guarnizo se prepara para ser
father The Westcolm bodyguard who
padre El guardaespaldas de westcolm que
threatened to give the review ends up in
amenazó a dar la review acaba en la
jail all this and much more here on your
cárcel todo esto y mucho más aquí en tu
favorite gossip channel What's up my
canal de chisme favorito Qué pasa mi
kids How are you guys wow how
chavalería Cómo estáis vaya tela cómo
the last few days are going wow how
están los últimos días vaya tela como
the whole month is going in fact it seems to me that this
está el mes entero de hecho me parece
is the record month that we are
que es el mes en récord que estamos
doing in my entire YouTube history
haciendo en toda mi historia de YouTube
in all the years that I have been here in
en todos los años que llevo aquí en la
life by the way I continue collecting By the
vida por cierto sigo recopilando Por
way, thank you very much for the support in
cierto muchas gracias por el apoyo en
the last videos I have to say that I
los últimos vídeos tengo que deci que
continue  gathering information and that I continue
sigo recopilando información y que sigo
doing my research And that there will
haciendo mis investigaciones Y que
soon be a new video if you want it to
pronto habrá nuevo vídeo si queréis que
come quickly prove it to me with a good
venga rápido demostrármelo con un buen
like and a subscription I am Javier
like y una suscripción soy Javier
Oliveira Welcome to my
oliveira Bienvenidos a mi canal
main channel if you didn't know me then
principal si no me conocías pues
welcome here we talk about all the
bienvenido aquí hablamos de todo el
gossip and everything that
chisme del cotilleo y de todo lo que se
goes viral on the internet and you will find out
haga viral en internet y te enterarás
here before anywhere else about
aquí antes que en cualquier sitio de
all the fuss that is happening
todo el jaleo que esté pasando en el día
today I feel like it I feel like it I'm
de hoy se me apetece se me apetece te
going to give you a video game stay
voy a regalar un videojuego estate
tuned throughout the video because at
pendiente a lo largo del vídeo que en
any moment Random a
cualquier momento Random aparecerá un
code will appear that you can redeem only if you
código que puedes canjear solamente si
are the fastest of this I won't
eres el más rápido de lo este no me
go on any longer because today's video is
enrollo más que el vídeo de hoy viene
loaded make yourself comfortable And let's get down to business to
cargadito ponte cómodo Y vamos al lío a
see the first topic that we are going to comment on it
ver el primer tema que vamos a comentar
seems like a fantasy to me It turns out
a mí me parece una fantasía Resulta ser
that Ricky Eddy since Dallas
que a Ricky Eddy desde que Dallas lo ha
challenged him to a debate in person or on a
retado a un debate en persona o en
call whatever they can do, they won't stop coming up with
llamada como sea no paran de ocurrirsele
the best excuses I've ever seen in my
las mejores excusas que he visto en mi
life better from the town with that I say it
vida mejo del pueblo con eso lo digo
all from the creators of I'm going to
todo de los creadores de me voy al
town or I'm going to sleep the order has arrived
pueblo o me voy a dormir ha llegado la
of distancing
orden de alejamiento
well I don't know if he's referring to a
bien no sé si se está refiriendo a
debate he's not referring to a
debate no se está refiriendo a una
call he's not referring to a
llamada no se está refiriéndose una
fight I don't know what he's receiving But
pelea No sé qué está recibiendo Pero
first of all well do you all have permission to call me a
antes de nada bueno tenéis permiso todos
coward to call me a
los pancitos para llamarme cobarde para
liar to call me a [ __ ]
llamarme mentiroso para llamarme cagado
to call me previous videos because I
para llamarme videos anteriores porque
can't share all the information
no puedo compartir toda la información
that I would like but currently for
que querría pero actualmente por motivos
legal reasons I can't be with Dallas in the
legales no puedo estar con Dallas en un
same place doing anything since of course it's
mismo sitio haciendo cualquier cosa
Pau wow wow wow okay okay okay
puesto por supuestísimo que es Pau guau
okay I understand that
guau guau vale vale vale vale entiendo
with these words you want to
que esto con estas palabras te queriendo
tell me that he really wants to debate well I do
decir que de verdad quiere debatir bien
n't know if he's referring to a debate he
no sé si se está refiriendo a debate no
's not referring to a call he's not
se está refiriendo a una llamada no se
referring to a fight I don't know what he's
está refiriéndose una pelea No sé qué
receiving But first of all well do you
está recibiendo Pero antes de nada bueno
all have permission to
tenéis permiso todos los pancitos para
call me a coward to call me a liar to call me a
llamarme cobarde para llamarme mentiroso
[ __ ] to call me
para llamarme cagado para llamarme
previous videos
videos anteriores
because I can't share all the
porque no puedo compartir toda la
information that I would like but currently
información que querría pero actualmente
for legal reasons I can't be with
por motivos legales no puedo estar con
Dallas in the same place doing
Dallas en un mismo sitio haciendo vídeo
live video this of course let's see if it does
en directo esto por supuestísimo a ver
n't occur to you  tell me that this
que no se os ocurra decirme que esto no
isn't wonderful this is a fantasy not
es maravilloso esto es una fantasía no
only has he done this reacting to the
solamente ha hecho esto reaccionando al
video in which Dallas challenges him to a debate
vídeo en el que Dallas le reta a debatir
but in real life according to what they are
sino que en la vida real según nos están
telling us Ricky would have done the same thing it
contando Ricky habría hecho lo mismo
turns out that the other night delux who you
resulta que la otra noche delux al que
all know Now because of this
todos conocéis Ya por el tema este de
podcast thing and I can say this because
los podcast y esto lo puedo decir porque
de log stopped by the chat the other day
de log se pasó el otro día por el chat
and said he had
del canijo y lo dijo había quedado por
dinner with Ricky Eddy that night It seems
la noche a cenar con Ricky Eddy Parece
that Adelo came up with the idea that it would be a
ser que adelo se le ocurre que sería
good idea to tell Dallas that he was having
buena idea avisar a Dallas de que estaba
dinner with Ricky Eddy to propose to
cenando con Ricky Eddy para proponerle a
Dallas that he stop by there Dallas with
Dallas que se pasara por allí Dalas con
the joke he has said yes he would
la Guasa que tiene le dijo que sí que se
stop by there even if it was just to say
pasaba por allí aunque fuera para
hello to Ricky Eddy or whatever okay
saludar a Ricky Eddy o lo que sea vale
where he is signing publicly and
donde va firmando de forma pública y
privately that he has a
Privada que tiene una orden de
restraining order against me he has said this
alejamiento contra mí esto lo ha dicho
so much in one of his last videos that he
tanto en uno de sus últimos vídeos que
is self-destructing in his videos
se está autodestruyendo en sus vídeos
as he has said it to colleagues coworkers
como se lo ha dicho a colegas compañeros
that we have in common who
de trabajo que tenemos en común los
were going to have dinner with him and one of
cuales iban a cenar con él y uno de
these suggests do you want to come to
estos me propone quieres venir a
greet him at the beginning I told him no between
saludarle al inicio le dije que no entre
jokes but then I said you don't know what go on
bromas pero luego dije no sabes que dale
like that I'll pass to fill in a little and then I'll
así paso a rellenar un poco y luego me
go tell me I had been
voy me cuentas Ya hacía días que le
proposing to do a debate for days and he
había propuesto hacer un debate y lo
had completely ignored him despite the fact
había ignorado por completo a pesar de
that his fans were sending it to him on
que sus fans se lo estaban enviando por
Twitter, I mean they were tweeting and
Twitter o sea estaban tuiteando y
posting everywhere and Ricky
posteando en todos sitios y Ricky se
refused Rick started saying that he can't
negó Ricky se puso a decir que no puede
be in the same place as
estar en un mismo sitio donde esté
Dallas because there is a
Dallas porque hay una orden de
legal restraining order I told him to say that and
alejamiento legal le dije eso dijera y
his response was Ricky told me that he ca
Su respuesta fue Ricky me ha dicho que
n't legally be in the same place
no puede estar legalmente el mismo lugar
as you which made me
que tú lo cual me hizo una gracia
extremely funny at first I thought it
extrema en un primer momento pensé que
was because he had sued me for
era porque me había denunciado por
defaming him But that didn't make
difamarle Pero eso no tenían sentido
any sense at the end of the day you can
ninguno a fin de cuentas puedes
sue someone and that prevents you from
denunciar a alguien y eso te impide
being in the same place as that person
estar en el mismo lugar que esa persona
what my friend ended up telling me was that he couldn't do the same room as me because he had a restraining order against me he is a lawyer studying law you will see how this doesn't make any kind of [ __ ] sense at all the laughs I had at that moment made no
que tuve en ese momento no tuvieron
sense None of me laughed so much that I must have
sentido Ninguno me reí tanto que debía
like a crazy person in the middle of the
haber parecido un loco en medio de la
street who can't be in the same
calle que no pueden estar en la misma
room or on the same video call
habitación ni en la misma videollamada
or anything like that. I can't use the internet with this. The
ni nada por el estilo yo con esto no
best thing in life, uh, there
puedo internet lo mejor de la vida eh en
are many epic moments on the internet.
internet hay muchos momentos épicos
I consider that this is one of, let's see,
Considero que este es uno de a ver lo
first of all,
primero de todo es que las órdenes de
restraining orders don't work that way, the
alejamiento no funcionan de esa forma el
fact that you file a complaint against
hecho de que tú le pongas una denuncia a
someone because they have threatened you,
alguien porque te haya amenazado
taking into account that in any case,
teniendo en cuenta que fuera el caso
okay, I was already explaining in the
vale que ya estaba explicando en los
previous videos that this has no
vídeos anteriores que eso no tiene
effect whatsoever in this case, let it be known
recorrido ninguno en este caso vaya por
that I am completely
delante que estoy completamente en
against violence and all those
contra de la violencia y de todas esas
things, okay. Peace out, guys. Here we are
cosas vale Paz chavales Aquí somos
Pacifico. I'm legal until they piss me off,
Pacífico yo soy legal hasta que me tocan
but the thing is that it has no
los [__] pero es que no tiene ningún
effect whatsoever. These are two
tipo de recorrido es que son dos
people who have been sleeping with each other for
personas que se están tirando de hace
many years and it's a battle that
muchos años y es una batalla que inicia
Ricky starts. In fact, Dalas is the first
Ricky de hecho es que Dalas el primer
video he makes, but well, in this
vídeo que le hace pero bueno en este
video, leaving the debate aside, so is
vídeo dejando de lado el debate Así es
a complaint viable or not? A
viable o no una denuncia es que una
restraining order doesn't work like that, they're not
orden de alejamiento no funciona así no
going to grant you a
te van a conceder una orden de
restraining order for that, much less in an
alejamiento por eso y mucho menos en una
afternoon, but, whatever, but  Ricky, who do you
tarde pero o sea pero Ricky tú que te
think that restraining orders are
crees que la orden de alejamiento se
ordered like pizzas that you order
piden como las pizzas que tú la encargas
by phone and get delivered by balloon?
por teléfono y te la traes de globo que
No, kid, that doesn't work like that, my
no chiquillo que eso no funciona así mi
life, there are people in real danger,
vida que hay gente en peligro real en
imminent danger, who are not
peligro inminente a las que no se les
granted it, why do they consider a
concede para que consideran una orden de
restraining order? The authorities have to
alejamiento las autoridades tienen que
see a real imminent danger and apart
ver un peligro inminente real y aparte
from that, that takes its bureaucracy, its
de eso que eso lleva su burocracia sus
paperwork and its moves and they don't give it to you right
trámite y sus movidas y no te la dan así
away, this guy thinks that because he
al momento este se ha creído que como
has money or how he hesitates about having it,
tiene dinero o como vacila de tenerlo
you can go to El Corte Inglés and
que te puedes ir al corte inglés y
choose the restraining order that
eligen la orden de alejamiento que más
you like the most, the one that is your favorite color.
te guste la que sea de tu color favorito
No, Ricky, my life, that doesn't work, make up
no Ricky mi vida eso no cuela invéntate
another story, make up something else or don't
otra movida invéntate otra cosa o no te
make anything up, damn it's the [ __ ] debate that you've
inventes nada [__] es el [__] debate del
been blundering about for two years that Dallas
que llevas vacilando dos años que Dallas
was on the run, there you have it, the [ __ ]
estaba huyendo ahí lo tienes el [__]
debate. Go for it, what happens is
debate Dale caña lo que pasa es que
that now the debate is no longer going to be about
claro que ahora el debate ya no va a
how much a camera to
tratar de lo que cuesta una cámara para
record the rewin costs, but now the debate
grabar el rewin sino que ahora el debate
is going to be about what you're going to try.
va a tratar de que vas a intentar
defend yourself and try to convince us
defenderte e intentar convencernos de
that you believe your girlfriend's excuse that she has
que te crees a tu novia la excusa que te
given you because she has
ha puesto porque te ha puesto los
cheated on you against that a
cuernos contra que una orden de
restraining order must be notified since
alejamiento debe ser notificada ya que
if you violate the time in restraining for
si infringes la hora en alejamiento por
violating it but added to this it
incumplirla pero es que añadido a esto
has also been this clown ricuc
además ha sido este payaso el ricuc
who has been threatening me since
quien ha estado amenazándome a del año
2015 both publicly and privately he
2015 tanto por público por privado lo
would be doing it solely and exclusively
estaría haciendo única y exclusivamente
because it has [ __ ] him up in the soul the only
porque le ha [__] en el alma el único
video that I have dedicated to him after 30 of
vídeo que le he dedicado después de 30
his Where he has left him exposed for being
suyos Donde ha dejado expuesto por ser
a psychological abuser and I continue to
un maltratador psicológico y lo sigo
subscribe to him And that's what I do to him so much that I
suscribiendo Y eso le hago yo tanto que
had filed that complaint If he were that afraid of
había puesto esa denuncia Si tanto miedo
me I mean if he were so afraid
Me tuviera O sea si tanto miedo tuviera
of me as to request a
contra mí como para solicitar una orden
restraining order for telling him during a debate
alejamiento por decirle hace un debate
in person literally this
en persona literalmente esto no me
would not be dedicating a video to me a day
estaría dedicando un vídeo al día
for a whole week which is what it
durante una semana entera que es lo que
is right now on his channel it is a single topic
es ahora mismo en su canal es monotema
solely and exclusively about me people
única y exclusivamente sobre mí gente
who have even followed him for a long time
que incluso hace tiempo que le sigue
are literally making fun of him
literalmente está burlando de él
saying What are you doing man that you are
diciendo Qué haces tío que es que estás
looking really bad and the guy keeps
quedando muy mal y el tío sigue
doing it Likewise because I am going through it
haciéndolo Igualmente porque yo lo está
The bad thing is you see how
pasando Lo malo o sea Tú lo ves como
slowly his face degrades throughout
lentamente su cara se degrada a lo largo
the videos and the guy is worse all the time
de los vídeos y el tío está todo el rato
And on top of that he has unfollowed his
peor Y encima se ha dejado de seguir con
ex or girlfriend you don't even know if they have
la ex o novia ya ni siquiera sabes se
started unfollowing him again
han vuelto dejar de seguir otra vez
because conversations have come out that would
porque han salido conversaciones que
also prove that the ex really
demostraría además que la ex realmente
was unfaithful and it wasn't, it was not any
fue infiel y no fueron no fue ningún
type of abuse it's August and the
tipo de abuso estamos en agosto y los
courts and lawyers don't work in
juzgados y abogados no trabajan en
August this is a cheap excuse that he
agosto esto es una excusa barata que
is making up so that
está montando para que los tontitos de
his stupid fans will believe Oh it's true Ricky
sus fans se crean Ay es verdad Ricky no
can't do a debate in person with
puede hacer un debate en persona con
Dallas because legally he can't it's a
Dallas porque legalmente no puede es
lie he's lying to you only
mentira os está mintiendo únicamente
because he's scared It's so simple he's not
porque tiene miedo Así es simple no
afraid of being humiliated
tiene miedo a quedar humillado
basically what would happen is a tremendous
básicamente lo que pasaría tremendo
crybaby I mean you dedicate 30 videos to him and I make
llorón O sea me dedicas 30 vídeos le
one for me because he feels
hago uno y a mí porque él se siente
threatened he should shut his mouth already what are
amenazado que se calle la boca ya qué
you going to watch this video as soon as I
vas a ver este vídeo nada más lo
publish it I want to see right now that your
publique Quiero ver ahora mismo que tu
next post is Exactly that same
siguiente post sea Exactamente esa misma
restraining order I want to see it don't
orden de alejamiento quiero verla no
say Oh illegally I can't legally
digas Ah ilegalmente no puedo legalmente
yes you can you can publish that I want to
sí puedes puedes publicar eso quiero
see it where are you now restraining a
verlo dónde estás ahora alejamiento una
perfect representation of  that already seriously it does
perfecta representación de lo que ya
n't work like that
fuera de coña es que no funciona así Es
A restraining order doesn't work like
que una orden de alejamiento no funciona
that and it's not like I'm telling you that it's a
así y no es que te lo diga yo que sea un
gossip channel You can
canal de salseo Es que le podéis
ask any lawyer,
preguntar a cualquier abogado a
any jurist or any
cualquier jurista o a cualquier
law student it's not like that it's not
estudiante de derecho es que no es así
true the only reason that
es que no es verdad el único motivo que
can cross my mind why
se me puede pasar por la cabeza por el
Ricky shouldn't coincide
que Ricky no debería coincidir en algún
with Dallas somewhere legally speaking legally speaking
sitio con Dallas a modo legal hablando a
is that when
modo legal es que cuando se van a tomar
legal measures of any kind are going to be taken then it's
medidas legales de cualquier tipo pues
best that you don't continue crossing
lo mejor es que no te siga cruzando
posts with him, I mean for
publicaciones con él es decir por
example if Ricky intends to sue
ejemplo si Ricky pretende demandar a
Dallas he shouldn't do a collaboration
Dallas no debería hacer una colaboración
with him a debate with him arguing the
con él un debate con él discutiendo los
two because he wants to take it legally
dos porque lo quiere llevar por Lo legal
but even if that were the case
pero es que aunque eso fuera así
then he shouldn't be uploading
entonces tampoco debería estar subiendo
videos answering Dallas uploading
vídeos contestándole al Dallas subir
videos answering Dallas with the
vídeos contestando la Dallas con las
things she's saying harms him
cosas que está diciendo le perjudica
Exactly the same as coinciding with
Exactamente lo mismo que coincidir con
him or having a debate with him is not
él o hacer un debate con él no está
telling the truth by the way after
diciendo la verdad por cierto después de
the exclusive that we gave yesterday or the day before
la exclusiva que dimos ayer o antes de
yesterday on this channel with its due
ayer en este canal con sus debidas
reactions from both parties as I already
reacciones de ambas partes como ya os
told you in the  previous video on the one hand I
conté en el vídeo anterior por un lado
was talking to Lali who tried to
estuve hablando con Lali que me intentó
convince me to delete the video and she
convencer de que eliminase el vídeo y me
flatly denied me and denied that
negó rotundamente y me desmintió esa
conversation that We were seeing that was
conversación que Estuvimos viendo que se
leaked Ricky for his part blocked me and
filtró Ricky por su parte me bloqueó y
well he got very offended because he says
bueno se ofendió muchísimo porque dice
that I did not contrast the information with him that I do
que yo no contraste con él la
not have to
información que yo contigo no tengo que
contrast anything with you Ricky is that the
contrastar nada Ricky es que las
conversations were about Lali the
conversaciones eran de Lali las
conversations were between Lali and the
conversaciones eran entre Lali y la
people who were at the party I do
gente que estuvo en la fiesta yo contigo
not have to contrast anything with you as they
no tengo que contrastar nada como ya te
are already telling you on Twitter you did not
están diciendo en Twitter tú no
contrast anything when you decided to
contrastaste nada cuando decidiste
believe wismichu when he published my
creerte al wismichu cuando publicó mis
private conversations with other
conversaciones privadas con otras
people that also had their context
personas que También tenían su contexto
that I also explained and you moved on from the
que también lo explique y pasaste del
subject and decided to insult me ​​call me a
tema y decidiste insultarme llamarme
dirty old man on your Stream with much less
viejo verde en tu Stream con mucho menos
respect much infinitely less
respeto muchísimo infinitamente menos
Respect than I am dealing with the
Respeto del que estoy tratando yo el
subject and I did not block you or start
tema y yo no te bloqueé ni me puse a
whining But anyway what I was going to say that does
lloriquear Pero bueno lo que iba que eso
not matter to me the news immediately
no me importa la noticia inmediatamente
after that they have stopped
después de eso se han vuelto a dejar de
following each other on social networks after an
seguir en redes sociales después de un
exhaustive analysis We salseros have come
exhaustivo análisis Hemos llegado los
to the conclusion that  that apart
salseros a la conclusión de que aparte
from unfollowing the last person
de dejaros de seguir a la última persona
that Lali followed on her
que ha seguido Lali en sus redes
social networks, that's
sociales es
me alia sicora there is
ese soy yo alia sicora hay
nothing about this information that I just
en nada sobre esta información que os
gave you Dalas has posted a tweet
acabo de dar Dalas ha puesto un twit
laughing and making fun of himself he has also
riéndose y cachondeándose también ha
uploaded a video making fun of Ricky
subido un vídeo burlándose de Ricky
Edith comparing him to a servant guys
Edith comparándolo con un siervo chicos
we are traveling and we just saw
estamos de viaje y acabamos de ver a
Ricky on the side of the highway
Ricky en el arcén de la autopista
my goodness and while Ricky is
madre mía y mientras que Ricky está
dedicating his channel to giving Lali is
dedicando su canal a dar Lali está
making these publications that you are
haciendo estas publicaciones que estáis
seeing on the screen changing light
viendo en pantalla cambiando de luz
publishing some reflections and so on and
publicando alguna reflexiones y demás y
sharing tweets in which they
compartiendo tweets en los que le dan la
agree with her about the controversy and
razón a ella sobre la polémica y
deny those conversations that she
desmienten esas conversaciones que ella
signs are false René ZZ a youtuber who
firma son falsas René ZZ un youtuber que
is breaking it in a very short time has
lo está petando en muy poco tiempo ha
gained more than a million and a half
conseguido más de un millón y medio de
subscribers and has also wanted to give his
suscriptores y también ha querido dar su
opinion on this controversy despite the fact
opinión sobre esta polémica a pesar de
that he does not usually get involved in gossip or at
que no suele meterse mucho en salseos o
least comment on this type of
por lo menos comentar este tipo de
moves René wanted to give
movidas René ha querido regalarle a
Ricky Eddy a message in which he
Ricky Eddy un mensaje en el que le
advises him that  have a little
aconseja que tenga un poco de amor
self love that prevails a little in
propio que se imponga un poco en las
relationships that you don't always have to
relaciones que no siempre te tienes que
let yourself be trampled on and that all of us at some
dejar pisotear y que todos en alguna
point in our lives have been
ocasión en nuestra vida hemos sido
deceived and we also have to go through
engañados y tenemos que pasar también
these types of experiences I believe that in
por este tipo de experiencias yo creo
order for us to learn I mean if you don't go through
que para que aprendamos O sea si no pasa
these things you don't learn you don't know what it's like to be
por estas cosas no aprenden no saben lo
deceived you don't gain
que es que te engañen no coges
enough experience Not because I've lived through exactly the
bastante No por haber vivido Exactamente
same thing but because I see it I see it as
lo mismo sino porque lo veo lo veo peli
dangerous the matter is not a little I want I
agudo el asunto no es un poco Quiero
want to shed a little light on this
quiero dar un poco de luz sobre este
subject of relationships based on my
tema de las relaciones en base a mi
experience We have all suffered we have all been
experiencia Todos hemos sufrido a todos
deceived we have all been
nos han engañado a todos nos han
fooled we have all been hidden a thousand
vacilado a todos nos han ocultado mil
things from us we have to understand who we
cosas hay que entender a quién le
dedicate our time to because we
dedicamos nuestro tiempo porque se lo
dedicate it to them And to what extent we are going to
dedicamos Y hasta qué punto vamos a
deal with certain things okay for me one of
lidiar con ciertas cosas vale Yo una de
the greatest
las mayores
lessons I have had in my life has
lecciones que he tenido en mi vida ha
been learning to say no and
sido el aprender a decir que no y el
learning to impose myself when people
aprender a imponerme cuando la gente
try to let's say step on me too much but
intenta digamos pisarme demasiado pero
in the end when you are very cool The
al final cuando eres muy buena onda El
example of shaking hands and having your
ejemplo de dar la mano y que te coman el
arm eaten off, having your Pirul eaten off I don't
brazo que te coman el Pirul no me
remember what that phrase was I am the
acuerdo cómo era esa frase soy el
personified example of that I am a
ejemplo personificado de eso yo soy una
zero conflictive person And that girl
persona cero conflictiva Y esa chica
has infinite energy and she ends up like
tiene energía infinita y te acaba como
walking all over you and sees that you are being defeated
pasando por encima y ve que te derrota
in debates in daily fights and
el debates en trifulcas del día a día y
such there comes a point where she might
tal llega un punto en el que igual te
lose respect for you because you never put your foot down
pierde el respeto porque tú no te pones
and that is when in the
nunca y en ese momento es cuando al
end she ends up hesitating she ends up deceiving you by
final pues acaba vacilando te acaba
taking it out there I think that
engañando sacando por ahí yo creo que
these things serve to teach you I
estas cosas te sirven para aprender yo
think that sincerely Ricky does not
creo que sinceramente Ricky tampoco se
believe what is happening to him I am
cree lo que está pasando lo lamento
truly sorry I mean I am
mucho de verdad O sea lo lamento
truly sorry I am not happy that
muchísimo no me alegro de que le pase
this is happening to anyone but he is locking himself away he
esto a nadie pero se está encerrando la
is paying for it with all the people today he uploaded
está pagando con toda la gente hoy subió
a video on my secondary channel an
un vídeo en mi canal secundario un
excerpt and the truth is that he is
extracto y que la verdad es que nos está
insulting everyone he is
insultando a todo el mundo se está
taking things very badly I understand
tomando las cosas muy mal yo entiendo
that it is wrong that he is having a very bad time
que esté mal que lo esté pasando muy mal
but the thing is that he is paying for it with everyone
pero es que lo está pagando con todo el
except his girlfriend I mean what
mundo menos con la novia o sea lo que le
happened to him with his girlfriend he is paying for it
ha pasado con la novia lo está pagando
with everyone boy wake up what I
con todo el mundo chico espabila a lo
mean is that if you know
que me refiero es que si tú te conoces a
yourself and do your daily work and
ti mismo y haces tu trabajo diario y
know  to the person you are with And
conoces a la persona con la que estás Y
you have good communication the
tienes una buena comunicación las
chances of that failing are
probabilidades de que eso fracase son
lower Because that way you are going to
menores Porque esa manera te vas a dar
realize a lot of things that you don't
cuenta de muchísimas cosas de las que no
realize when you simply see life
te das cuando simplemente ves la vida
go by and you look at your partner and say God, this is what I
pasar y miras a tu pareja y dices Dios
've always dreamed of
es que es con lo que he soñado siempre
What is it that you've always dreamed of
Qué es con lo que has soñado siempre
To what extent it is pathological Where does
Hasta qué puntos patológico es De dónde
that come from You are projecting the image of
viene eso estás proyectando la imagen de
your mother onto your girlfriend These are
tu madre en tu novia son traumas
childhood traumas Why do you like what you like Why do you
infantiles Por qué te gusta lo que te
reject what you reject It is
gusta porque rechazas lo que rechazas es
very important to know all that because that's when
muy importante saber todo eso porque ahí
you start to realize a lot of things
te empiezas a dar cuenta de muchas cosas
Therapy helps a lot with that Reading
la terapia ayuda mucho a eso leer
Reflecting Meditating Lately he's been very
reflexionar meditar últimamente anda muy
naughty and very funny It
travieso y muy gracioso
turns out that in the last few days he had
Resulta ser que en los últimos días
been growing a mustache until they
había estado dejando un bigote hasta que
told him on Stream that he looked like
le han dicho en Stream que se parecía
Ricky Eddy with that mustache
con Ese bigote a Ricky Eddy
Immediately he got up from
inmediatamente carché se ha levantado de
his chair and went to take it off but
su silla y ha ido a quitárselo pero
well as if it were
bueno como si se tratara aquello de un
Velcro it came off in one go
velcro se le ha quitado de un tirón
Obviously he wants to be nominated for
evidentemente él quiere que lo nominen a
clip of the year for the wires and he's
clip del año para los alambres y ha
been asking for the Ricky  Eddy
estado pidiendo la Ricky Eddy que por
please don't make a video it's
favor no le saque un vídeo que
just humor I know I know I know I know he's
simplemente es humor lo sé lo sé
not going to Island I know I know I know It's okay
lo sé lo sé no se va para Island lo sé
don't make a video for me Ricky please It's
no me hagas un vídeo Ricky porfa Es un
humor it's humor
humor es humor
I feel like another video I released a
tengo ganas de otro vídeo he sacado un
clip on tiktok in which he has commented on
clip en tiktok en el cual ha comentado
internet personalities and celebrities for saying that women are
internet por decir que las mujeres son
fans of Hello Kitty and liars
fans de Hello Kitty y mentirosas
any other more I want more videos
cualquier otro más la quiero más videos
[Laughs]
[Risas]
at least five years
menos cinco años
apart from that he has been mocking and
aparte de eso se ha estado mofando y
celebrating the people who have fallen for his
celebrando la gente que ha caído en su
bytes back you have fallen again the Bye
bytes vuelto te has vuelto a caer el Bye
that we were explaining in the last
que estuvimos explicando en el último
video or in the last newscast And it turns
vídeo o en el último noticiero Y es que
out that karcher did a bait
resulta que karcher pues hizo un baiteo
to look for them to be funasen on purpose
para buscar que los funasen a propósito
and as a social experiment he did a
y como experimento social pues hizo un
couple of tiss in some he messed with
par de tiss en unos se metía con las
women in another he messed with men
mujeres en otro se metía con los hombres
with a lot of mantras and stereotypes
con un montón de mantras y estereotipos
and so on and the result we were
y demás y el resultado lo estuvimos
commenting on in the previous video So
comentando en el vídeo anterior Así que
if you missed it Go see it La Movida
si te lo perdiste Vete a verlo La Movida
que carches at the end explain that this  It has
que carches al final explica que esto le
served as a strategy and will
ha servido como estrategia y que va a
continue to do so to become
continuar haciéndolo para hacerse
relevant To become relevant again, they have
relevante Para volver a ser relevante
effectively denounced us for a
efectivamente nos han funado por un
batting,
bateo
applaud, gentlemen, we
aplaudir señores
did it, many
lo hicimos han caído ha caído mucha
people have fallen, many people have fallen, people who did not expect to
gente ha caído gente que no esperaba que
fall, people have fallen who later had to
cayese ha caído gente que luego han
delete Twitch but they have fallen, they have fallen,
tenido que borrar Twitch pero han caído
gentlemen, they have fallen there is a desire to screw me, we have shown it, there is a
ha caído señores han caído hay ganas de
desire to screw me, we have
ganas de darme por culo lo hemos
shown it and listen to me, we have
demostrado y escúchame hemos demostrado
also shown that you are dumb but we are here,
también que son bobis pero estamos aquí
applause for all of you, gentlemen,
un aplauso para todos ustedes señores lo
we have achieved it, even misogyny can be smelled
hemos conseguido hasta misoginia se
here, the
huele acá prácticamente lo decía el
Chihuahua from lesbie practically said it, they wanted to defend it,
Chihuahua de lesbie querían defenderlo
hahaha catcher Who are you? Okay, my friend, don't
Jajaja catcher Quién eres Ya amiguito no
even bother going on tiktok, see
se molesta ni meterse en el tiktok ver
the tweet and say how strange, they had always
el tweet y decir qué raro a mí siempre
told me that sarcasm and
me habían dicho que el Sarcasmo y el
sarcastic humor was humor for
humor sarcástico era humor para gente
intelligent people, but I thought it was something
inteligente pero yo pensaba que era algo
normal, but seeing these
como normal pero es que viendo estas
things, in the end I am going to believe that saying,
cosas al final me voy a creer ese dicho
in the end, but we know you, it is
al final pero te conocemos que es
different. It is not that it is different, let's
distinto No es que sea distinto vamos a
see that you cannot take seriously being
ver que no te puedes tomar en serio que
called a fan of Hello  Kitty and [ __ ] at the
te digan fan del Hello Kitty y [__] a la
same time no it's noticeable that her
misma vez que no que se nota que su
humor Damn You can't take it
humor [__] Que no te lo puedes tomar en
seriously I don't believe it I don't believe
serio que no me lo creo no me lo creo
the expressions no I'm looking for what I
las expresiones no Yo estoy buscando lo
'm looking for I already said it yesterday I
que estoy buscando yo ya lo dije ayer yo
already said it yesterday what we have to
ayer ya lo dije nosotros lo que tenemos
do now is make bytes
que hacer ahora es hacer bytes de
okay that go viral and that's how we
acuerdo que se hagan virales y así
gain relevance by making
ganamos relevancia haciendo bateos
viral hits Look yesterday People have already fallen that's it we have to
virales Mira ayer Ya cayeron gente ya
go up then she
está hay que hay que ir subiendo luego
was also starring alongside
también estuvo protagonizando junto a
Aby in some marriage scenes typical
Aby unas escenas de matrimonio típicas
of the Antena 3 series first they had
de la serie de Antena 3 primero tuvieron
a little argument over the
discutiendo un poco por el lugar de las
vacation location and it seems that Aby
vacaciones y es que parece ser que Aby
has some complaint that she has to
tiene alguna queja que le tiene que
always propose
proponer siempre los planes de
vacation plans on Stream to put him in a
vacaciones en Stream para ponerlo en
difficult position in front of the audience
compromiso delante de la audiencia
because if not The kid doesn't want to
porque si no El chaval no se quiere
move we can look at it Eh well we
mover lo podemos mirar Eh pues lo
can look at it eh
podemos mirar eh
thanks for being here and making it possible for me to
gracias por estar aquí y hacer que pueda
make a plan with my husband can you stop
hacer un plan con mi marido podéis dejar
playing the victim I'm not the
de hacerte la víctima no soy la víctima
Supreme victim and I have to denounce you people
Suprema y te tengo que funar la gente lo
have said it I have to denounce you if not I wouldn't be
ha dicho tengo que funarte si no no
fulfilling my role in
estaría cumpliendo mi papel en las
relationships Of course apart from that Abby  had to
relaciones Claro aparte de eso Abby tuvo
clarify that he has never hit carché
que aclarar que nunca ha pegado a carché
because the kid is afraid of
porque al chiquillo le da miedo las
bottles, in other words, Abi grabs a bottle from
botellas o sea Abi coge una botella de
her desk to ask karcher to
su escritorio para pedirle a karcher que
fill it up and karcher runs away
será llene y karcher sale corriendo
when he sees that bird grabs the bottle I do
cuando ve que ave agarra la botella
n't know if he thought it was Abi or if he was
no sé si se creía que era Abi o estaba
watching wismichu in that Setup
viendo wismichu en ese Setup
we went to the gym I
hemos ido al gimnasio
swear I've never hit
juro que nunca he pegado
judo I've never hit in
judo que nunca he pegado en situaciones
normal situations you have to manipulate yourself on steam
normales hay que manipularte en steam
so they make your tiktoks and the
para que te hagan los tiktoks y los
others eat for you crazy eh crazy let's
otros coman por ti locurita eh locurita
go viral my people thanks buddy
vamos virales mi gente gracias compañero
after that they play rock paper
después de eso se juegan a piedra papel
scissors to see who opens the door
o tijera a ver quién abre la puerta
when the food arrives
cuando llegue la comida
The first rock paper scissors
La primera piedra papel o tijera
Yeah man sure Here you stay that's not
Sí hombre claro Aquí te quedas eso no
worth it that's not worth it
vale eso no vale
up here
aquí arriba
what was this
que era esto
rock paper scissors 1 2 3 rock
piedra Papel o tijeras 1 2 3 piedra
paper scissors 1 2 3
papel o tijera 1 2 3
and later Abi jokes with her boyfriend and
y más tarde Abi bromea con su novio y se
jokes with him stating that
mete de broma con él afirmando que
karches is susim well do you think
karches es susim bueno ustedes creen que
that's a joke or is it a little true I'm
eso es broma o es un poquito verdad me
going to explain  what behavior has
voy a explicar qué comportamiento ha
Carlos had for you to call him an idiot it
tenido Carlos para que le llames huevón
's a simple of course it's that he's my partner
es un simple claro es que es mi pareja
that's how relationships work guys
es como funcionan las relaciones chicos
without mutual problem I know that there are many people who have a
sin pedo mutuo sé que hay mucha gente os
hard time understanding it but in a relationship you
cuesta entenderlo pero una relación tú
have to pamper you have to love you have to that is what there is we are
tienes que mimar tienes que querer
two Sims
tienes que es lo que hay somos dos Sims
him then with the other you are zero without
él luego con el otro tú eres cero sin
for him look at me
por él mira que se me pueden decir
many things eh you can tell me
muchas cosas eh se me pueden decir
many many things many many things you
muchas muchas cosas muchas muchísimas se
can insult me ​​for a thousand things that not
me pueden insuldar por mil cosas que no
always Carlos me me in another order of
siempre al Carlos yo yo en otro orden de
things It seems that the million has been
cosas Parece ser que al millón le han
offered the contract of his life and I say
propuesto el contrato de su vida y digo
the contract of his life because it is
el contrato de su vida porque no es
no secret and any streamer who is
ningún secreto y cualquier streamer que
dedicated to this knows that a person
se dedica a esto sabe que una persona
with the beagles who has the million earns
con los beagle que tiene el millón gana
a lot of money and apparently he has decided to
bastante pasta y al parecer ha decidido
try during the next month he is going to
probar durante el siguiente mes va a
approve For a whole month in Kick
aprobar Durante un mes entero en Kick O
So they had to offer him so
sea que le han tenido que ofrecer para
that he takes the risk on this and well we'll
que se arriesgue a esto y bueno veremos
see how it goes the truth is that I
a ver cómo sale la verdad es que yo lo
see it complicated he says that he is going to extend
veo complicado él dice que va a ampliar
the time that he is going to be full Stream that he is going to
el tiempo que va a estar full Stream que
dedicate many hours to streaming the
va a dedicar muchas horas a stremear el
LoL  and also many hours doing what are
LoL y también muchas horas hacer cómo se
called slots that if I'm not mistaken it is
llaman slot que si no me equivoco es el
this thing of the machines and the
tema este de las maquinitas y de las de
betting ones no, I mean the games of chance
las apuestas no o sea los juegos de azar
that I think that if you live in Spain you can't
que creo que eso si vives en España no
do it but well since he lives
lo puedes hacer pero bueno como él vive
in Andorra Well maybe there you
en andorra Pues a lo mejor Allí sí se
can people joke with him in the chat
puede la gente le bromea en el chat
saying that he won't even have 500
afirmando que no va a tener ni 500
viewers there but he is very clear about it he
viewer allí pero él lo tiene muy claro
feels very sure of himself and his
se siente muy seguro de sí mismo y de su
future in Kick and at any time I can I
futuro en Kick y en cualquier momento
can watch Twitch but we are going to
puedo puedo ver a Twitch pero vamos a
do a month of testing here but a little how it
hacer un mes de prueba aquí pero un poco
works how it goes 70,000 hours
qué tal funciona qué tal va 70.000 horas
a day of League of Legends 70,000 hours
al día de League of Legends 70.000 horas
a day of slots put in 14 hours a day of
al día de slots meter 14 horas al día de
Stream and see a little how everything works
Stream y ver un poco cómo funciona todo
how it goes What are the feelings What
cómo va Cuáles son los feelings Cuáles
are the amount of viewers What is the
son la cantidad de viewer Cuál es el
feedback from the viewers What is everything in
feedback de los viewers Cuál es todo en
general you know And from there we will see
general sabes Y a partir de ahí veremos
a little not even 500 live will have 500 viewers
un poco ni 500 vivos tendrá 500 viewers
will I have them lifetime in my starting are to
los tendré lifetime en mi starting son a
the 5 minutes In 10 years or in
los 5 minutos Dentro de 10 años o dentro
20 years with 50 years playing League
de 20 años con 50 años jugando al League
ofLegends
of Legends
chat I am still a [ __ ] streamer Ari
chat soy un fucking de streamer aún Ari
Gameplay has come out to deny that she
Gameplay ha salido a desmentir que ella
was participating in a
estuviera participando en una
conversation in a video call with
conversación en una videollamada con
other streamers in which they were
otras streamers en la que estaban
making fun of what had happened
cachondeándose de lo que le había pasado
to i Speed ​​show who is this
a i Speed show que es el streamer este
very powerful streamer from North America who the other
tan potente de Norteamérica que el otro
day was like celebrating I don't know what
día estaba como celebrando una no sé qué
in a game and Tula got like that he did
en una partida y se le puso la Tula así
n't get well Tula got
no se puso bueno se puso la Tula por ahí
naughty there no by the way in the video I
traviesa no que por cierto en el vídeo
said good you Spring and you were all
dije buena tú la Spring y estabais todos
freaking out in the comment box saying
rayado en la caja de comentario diciendo
but when Spring Tula came out well
pero cuando se ha sacado Spring la Tula
any day now she will also escape
pues cualquier día se le escapa también
pri around there the third leg we don't
a pri por ahí la tercera pierna no lo
know if they appear now
sabemos si aparecen ahora se termina el
world hunger is over if she appears now we
hambre mundial si aparece ahora nos
like penis
gusta el pene
the fact is that in that video call that
el hecho es que en esa videollamada que
has gone viral there are several
se ha viralizado hay varios creadores de
content creators it is at 2 Geo cristal Molly
contenido está al 2 Geo cristal Molly
friendly and that she is arik's sister and
amable y que es la hermana de arik y se
the voices can be confused and there are many
pueden confundir las voces y hay mucha
people who have thought that Ari
gente que se ha pensado que Ari
Gameplays were there Also laughing
Gameplays estaba allí También riéndose
in fact what had happened to the
de hecho que le había ocurrido al
streamer
streamer
I did not see the video has nothing
yo no vi el video no tiene nada
what happened dude
lo que pasó güey
How much did he feel the cold
En cuánto sintió el frío
the breeze the air
la brisa el aire
Hey but they banned him I did not know if they banned him for
Oigan pero lo banearon yo no supe si lo
like half an hour shaking it out there
como media hora meneandola ahí de fuera
Maybe that lasted the video for you a
Quizás eso duró el video para ti un
loop analyzing dude
bucle analizando güey
Apparently for some reason that I do
Al parecer por algún motivo que
not know because watching This video The
desconozco porque viendo Este vídeo La
truth is that the call It is nonsense
verdad es que la llamada Es una tontería
and they are joking they would be defaming Ari for
y están de broma estarían funando a Ari
loving each other that she participated in that
por quererse que ella participaba en esa
call and the streamer has wanted to come out to
llamada y la streamer ha querido salir a
deny this hoax there is one thing that
desmentir este bulo hay una cosa que sí
I would like
me gustaría
really silly things they are throwing at me
cosas tontas de verdad me andan tirando
That because according to I threw or made fun of
Que porque según le tiré o me burle de
Speed ​​at what moment at what moment one they
Speed en qué momento en qué momento uno
are saying that I said something when I
están diciendo que yo dije algo cuando
was playing with more people and they are
estaba jugando con más gente y se están
confusing people to begin with, I
confundiendo de personas para empezar o
mean,
sea de
some games that had some people
unas partidas que tuvieron unas personas
that you do not tell me names Well it also
que no me decís nombres Pues también me
seems silly to me As if someone made a
parece tonto Como que alguien hizo un
comment they thought that I said it I
comentario pensaron que lo dije yo yo ni
was not even in that call I do not even know that I
siquiera estaba en esa llamada yo ni sé
was  playing that time So
que estaba jugando esa vez Entonces me
they're throwing me out for that and then they're
están tirando por eso y luego están
putting up an old clip of mine where I
poniendo un clip viejo mío de donde
was defending someone from an
estaba defendiendo de alguien de un
idiot from the chat who comes to insult me
tonto del chat que viene a insultarme
where I say something about a little pee and
donde digo algo de un pipí pequeño y
obviously you don't have to
obviamente
be stupid I even had another
no hay que ser tonto tenía hasta otro
hair I think I even had the
pelo creo que incluso tenía hasta el
other zero and people are throwing me out for
otro cero y la gente me está tirando por
that when I didn't even say anything
eso cuando yo ni siquiera dije nada
literally what I said about Speed ​​was Oh
literal lo que dije de Speed fue Ay
poor thing and And I mentioned that playing
pobrecito y Y eso lo mencioné jugando
with Dead and with Juan and in fact we were
con Dead y con Juan y de hecho estábamos
talking about how he was bothered
hablando de que a él le había molestado
that several content creators
que en varios creadores de contenido
were publishing his video I said Oh
estaban publicando su video Yo dije Ay
poor thing and that's what I said about him and they're
pobrecito y eso fue lo que dije de él y
telling me that I said I don't know what
me están diciendo que yo dije no sé qué
things in the troll Yeah well I don't care
cosas en la trolea Sí bueno Me vale
I just wanted to clarify that it wasn't me
madre solo quería aclarar que no era yo
but if you see a tiktok clip or
pero si viven algún clip de tiktok o
some idiot wanting to continue blaming me
algún menso queriendo seguirme culpando
for things that I don't do so that they can
de cosas que no hago para que me
defend me and say that it wasn't me who said
defiendan y digan que no fui yo que dije
anything about him yesterday We were watching how
nada de él ayer Estuvimos viendo como
Juan Guarnizo told his followers
Juan guarnizo contaba a sus seguidores
that he had had a specific call
que había tenido una llamada en concreto
that an A4 call had taken place in which
que había tenido lugar una llamada A4 en
both couples  they would have discussed
la que ambas parejitas habrían discutido
and debated about the differences they had
y debatido sobre las diferencias que
in recent months we already
habían tenido en los últimos meses ya
heard yesterday the way
escuchamos ayer la forma de contarlo que
Juan Guarnizo told it and Ari Gameplays has
tuvo Juan guarnizo y Ari Gameplays ha
also wanted to show her audience how
querido también mostrar a su público lo
happy she is about this
contenta que está por esta
Reconciliation words that Juan already said we
Reconciliación palabras que ya dijo Juan
had the opportunity to talk to
tuvimos la oportunidad de hablar con
Aurora or Bee Gees we are very
Aurora ni con Bee Gees estamos muy
happy we are very very happy
contentos estamos muy muy contentos
because really we missed each other a lot
porque de verdad Nos extrañábamos mucho
at the moment we
de momento
had the opportunity to talk to
tuvimos la oportunidad de hablar con
them we
ellos
told each other that we missed each other a lot
nos dijimos que nos extrañábamos mucho
that we did miss the friendship that we
que sí extrañamos la amistad que
had we are very happy we are
teníamos estamos muy contentos estamos
very happy As Juan said
muy contentos Como dijo Juan de
taking that weight off our shoulders was something we
quitarnos ese peso encima ya era algo
wanted as a mupón we
que queríamos como mupón nos dimos
also realized that it had no use
cuenta también que no había tenido caso
like the distancing so I am
como el distanciamiento entonces estoy
very happy I am very happy it made me very
muy feliz estoy muy feliz me hizo muy
happy to listen to Beijing especially
feliz escuchar a Beijing especialmente
I was excited to listen to her I know it is
me hacía ilusión escucharla me sé de
really excited to listen to her and nothing I am
verdad ilusión escucharla y nada estoy
very happy That does not mean that we are going to be
muy contenta Eso no significa que vamos
playing this week maybe not even
a estar jugando esta semana tal vez ni
next what is least is a matter of
la próxima lo que menos es es cosa de
streams it was more for us that we
streams era más por nosotros que
had our WhatsApp group there that
teníamos ahí nuestro grupo WhatsApp que
we talked very often and we had it
hablábamos muy seguido y lo teníamos
stopped and we are happy that we are back
parado y estamos felices de que ya
texting us then
volvimos a estar texteandonos entonces
I'm happy I'm quite happy and I
estoy feliz estoy bastante feliz y ya
just wanted you to know just like I
solo quería como que que lo supieran así
had talked about it a few days ago that
como lo había hablado Hace unos días de
well obviously it wasn't like before
que pues evidentemente no era como antes
well I also wanted to mention that
pues también quería mencionarles que
now we do talk and we were able to
ahora sí platicamos y pudimos como
express my opinion on this
expresarnos mi opinión respecto a este
subject well it's a little bit what I said yesterday
tema pues es un poco lo que dije ayer
It seems that on one hand he is more
Parece ser que por un lado está más
interested than the other in having
interesado que por el otro que se sepa
this Reconciliation known in fact the
de esta Reconciliación de hecho la
position of auronplay when he has been
postura de auronplay cuando le han
asked on Stream regarding this
preguntado en Stream respecto a este
approach has been quite different from that of
acercamiento ha sido bastante diferente
the couple
a la que ha tenido la parejita que
formed by Ari Gameplays and Juan Guarnizon
forman Ari Gameplays y Juan guarnizon
we are glad that you have been able to talk
nos da gusto que hayas podido hablar las
things over with Juanito it's always good to be
cosas con Juanito siempre es bueno estar
at peace with others Thank you I love you
en paz con los demás Gracias te quiero
Send a Korean heart to Estefanía
Mándale un corazón coreano a Estefanía
I don't usually talk about my
Yo es que no suelo hablar de mi vida
private life The truth is that I'm not going to say
privada La verdad ni tampoco voy a decir
much about it if you want a
mucho al respecto si queréis vida
private life I think you just have to go
privada creo que solo tenéis que entrar
on Twitter and you'll have a blast it's that I'm
en Twitter y os vais a poner las botas
not going to say anything the truth is I don't have to
es que no voy a decir nada la verdad no
say absolutely anything I mean
tengo que decir absolutamente nada o sea
my private life is my private life period it's that I
mi vida privada es mi vida privada y
don't have to say anything
punto es que no tengo que decir nada la
true I think there's no need to go into too
verdad yo creo que no hace falta entrar
many explanations and that the
en muchas explicaciones y que la
difference is Clara don't you believe on the other
diferencia es Clara no creéis por otro
hand Juan Guarnizo has been explaining
lado Juan guarnizo ha estado explicando
that lately he's been reading books to
que últimamente anda leyendo libros para
become more familiar with parenting
ir familiarizándose con la paternidad
watch out I already scared him of everything She's
ojo al canto Ya le di miedo de todo lo
surrounded by children what you
que Está rodeada con los hijos lo que tú
have to do is fill him with fears the
tienes que hacer es llenarlo de miedos
more fears the child has the less he's
entre más miedos tenga el niño menos se
going to dare to do something dangerous is
va a atrever a hacer algo peligroso es
a piece of advice that I give him I've been
un consejo que le suelto Yo he estado
reading a lot about parenting
leyendo mucho acerca de paternidad
yes
sí
How to handle different situations already in
Cómo manejar distintas situaciones ya en
normal life sincerely Although it may
la vida normal sinceramente Aunque
seem otherwise I don't think it's
parezca lo contrario yo no creo que sea
because they have plans to have children in the
porque tengan planes de tener hijos en
very near future in fact in an
un futuro muy próximo de hecho en una
interview that I did with Juan I don't know if it
entrevista que le hice a Juan no sé si
was the interview that I did or he
fue la entrevista que le hice o él en
was talking live I think it
algún directo estuvo hablando creo que
was in the interview that I did he was
fue en la entrevista que le hice estuvo
talking about that they wanted to enjoy
hablando que ellos querían disfrutar de
this until they were really mature it's
esto hasta bien hasta bien maduritos se
called maturing let's see not so
llama madurar a ver tampoco tan
mature but for example starting to
maduritos sino por ejemplo empezar a
have children until the limit not until
tener hijos hasta el límite no hasta los
40 or something like that and right now being
40 o cosas así y estar ahora mismo
focused on their work so I think it must have
centrados en su trabajo así que yo creo
been simple curiosity
que habrá sido simple curiosidad
surely you will remember to give  in I think that's
seguramente recordaréis a dar en creo
how it's pronounced if I'm not
que se pronuncia así era si no me
mistaken Westcold's bodyguard
equivoco El guardaespaldas de westcold
who in fact I think the role he played
que de hecho creo que el papel que jugó
in the videos that Dallas made for him I think
en los vídeos que Dallas le hizo creo
the role he played was like he was
que el papel que jugó era como que da la
joking that the two of them were boyfriend and girlfriend or
bromeaba con que los dos eran novios o
were having an affair or something like that Yeah we
estaban liados o algo por el estilo Sí
already heard that you love to suck the
ya escuchamos que te encanta comerte la
whole thing that you're really gay now please let's
entera que eres re gay ya por favor
move on to something else and he got like
pasemos a otra cosa y se puso como en
aggressive like he wanted to hit
plan agresivo de que quería pegarle a
Dallas surely you will remember that
Dallas seguramente recordaréis ese
episode that got you so upset
episodio que te alcance a molestar tanto
to say
para decir
and that's how he behaved because you
y así es como se comportabas porque
may not be good you're gay good
podrás que no ser bonos sos gay buenos
but that's crazy if you understand me I
pero eso es una loca sí me entendés o
mean you're a [ __ ] crazy you hit my
sea vos sos una [__] loca tú pegar mi sí
inner yes or no says that I would enjoy it a
o no interior dice que lo disfrutaría
lot yes you understand I mean yes yes but
bastante sí me entendés O sea sí sí pero
gay friends and apart from that they are really good
los amigos gay y aparte de eso son re
buddies because they always always have
parceros porque siempre siempre tienen
many friends they are always a
muchas amigas siempre siempre son un
good element always always
buen elemento siempre siempre
because they introduce you to women
porque te presentan las mujeres
disrespect It's something personal if you
faltar el respeto Es algo personal si me
understand me here they would hit you Peace that's a
entiende acá te pegarían Paz eso es un
nerd behind a computer looking for
nerd detrás de un computador buscando
people who he talks about there's no need to  I
gente de quien habla no hace falta que
explained to you again what I think about
os explique otra vez lo que pienso de la
people who when they have no arguments or
gente que cuando no tiene argumentos o
when you mess with them they want to
cuando te metes con ellos te quieren
hit you with real violence they want to
pegar con violencia real que te quieren
attack you anyway the profile is what it is it did
agredir en fin el perfil es el que es
n't take a genius to
tampoco hacía falta ser un lince para
realize it and It seems that this guy
cuenta y Parece ser que este chico ha
had a real fight in the street with a
tenido una pelea real en la calle con un
pedestrian he messed up and ended up in
viandante la ha liado y ha terminado en
jail so nothing good the partner they
la cárcel Así nada bueno el socio lo
put him in jail well they put him to
metieron a la cárcel pues lo metieron a
give like that swimming then he started fighting
dar así nadar entonces empezó a pelear
with a traffic I think you know
con un tránsito Yo creo que usted sabe
the story many and the [ __ ] Well the
la historia muchos y el [__] Pues la
truth the truth is the dude is the egg he did
verdad la verdad el parcero es el huevo
n't do anything to stop him they attacked him you
no hizo nada para lo atacaron me
know what I mean he just defended himself
entiende el más simplemente se defendió
And that's it and a fight and here in Spain if I'm not
Y ya y una pelea y aquí en España si no
mistaken if you take a threat to
me equivoco si tú llevas una amenaza a
real violence or rather if you hit
una violencia real o sea si tú le pegas
someone it depends To what extent it
a alguien depende Hasta qué punto
depends To what extent and how you do it
depende Hasta qué punto y cómo lo haga
whatever the context is you can also
cuál sea el contexto puedes también
end up arrested and you can hit yourself for a few
acabar detenido y puedes pegarte unos
days too lock yourself up hollow he
diitas también encerraete hueco le
explains to him that his friend asked him for help that he
explica que su amigo le pidió ayuda que
made the call to ask for help
le hizo la llamada para pedirle ayuda
but that he can't go to
pero que él no se puede pasar por la
jail because if  They recognize it could be
cárcel porque si lo reconocen podría ser
detrimental to both of us The thing is that they
perjudicial para ambos El caso es que a
called me and told me that
mí mismo me llamaron y me dijeron que
you can also called me and said daddy they're
puedes también me llamó y me dijo papi
going to put me in jail bro I need
van a meter a la cárcel bro Necesito
your help The first thing I told him is
ayuda suya Yo lo primero que le dije es
bro I can help you but I can't
bro Yo te puedo ayudar pero no puedo
show up over there you know If I go to
aparecerme por allá entiende Si yo voy a
jail over there dog really you
la cárcel allá perro de verdad ustedes
think I'm a movie whatever
creen que yo soy una película lo que sea
but the thing is that I know what I live through I go over
pero es que yo sé lo que yo vivo yo voy
there well not even a thousand police officers know me they
allá bueno ni a mil policía me conoce a
stop me in traffic the traffic
mí me para un tránsito a mí el tránsito
knows me I don't know who could be
me conoce yo no sé quién puede ser
malicious and daddy let's suppose that
malintencionado y papi supongamos que me
the person in charge knows me and
conoce la persona que si hay a cargo y
says let's not let us go here and ask for
diga no dejemos a dar en acá y pidamos
money that guy doesn't give it and it
plata que ese huevo no la da y le
complicated the way around for the guy
complicó la vuelta al parcero
just lazy Because I was you
simplemente huevón Porque yo fui
know people are very smart so
entiende la gente es muy viva entonces
right now I have to take care of everyone
ahorita me tengo que cuidar de todo el
family over here let's leave the
mundo familia por aquí vamos dejando el
video for today I think it's
videito por hoy Yo creo que está
quite loaded So tomorrow more and
bastante cargadete Así que mañana más y
better the good if it is brief twice
mejor lo bueno si es breve dos veces
Well and this video has not been
Bueno y este vídeo no ha tenido nada de
short at all so well Congratulations to whoever
breve así que bueno Enhorabuena al que
got the video game  Remember
le haya tocado el videojuego recuerda
that you can be the next. Here
que tú puedes ser el próximo aquí te
the editor will be showing you
estará poniendo el editor en pantalla
how to exchange it in case you are clumsy.
como canjearlo por si eres torpe
Remember that you can be the next.
recuerda que tú puedes ser el próximo
Subscribe by activating the bell to
suscríbete activando la campanita para
be the fastest to enter and for
ser el más rápido en entrar y que
YouTube to notify you every time I upload a
YouTube te notifique cada vez que subo
video. As I said, okay, family. I will be
vídeo lo dicho vale familia estaré
reading the comments box, your
leyendo la caja de comentarios vuestras
opinions on all the topics. I send you
opiniones sobre todos los temas os mando
a huge hug and bye bye.
un abrazo enorme y chao chao
[Music]
[Música]